[{"answer": "Then it seems we are not the only ones incapable of handling every situation the Stargate may present after all", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-48-Hours.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "All of them have been contacted successfully. SG5 and SG8 have already arrived safely", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Teal'c is an invaluable asset. Without him you might very well not be sitting there supposedly representing your country", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-48-Hours.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Teal'c is one of our own. And his life is not lost yet", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Now all we need to do is send one of our teams off on a sort of fac", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-48-Hours.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Allies of Earth", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I swear my friend", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-48-Hours.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Then who did", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-48-Hours.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "What do you know", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I didn't think you'd believe me any other way. And I wanted to warn you", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-48-Hours.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I heard about Teal'c", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "About what", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-48-Hours.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "What about it", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I'll be in town for a couple of days. I'd like to see how things turn out. I'm at the Accent Inn checked in under the name my friend", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-48-Hours.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Can I come in", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-48-Hours.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Clock's ticking. You have less than 32 hours", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "The difference is, it would take only one nuke to get through an ant", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-48-Hours.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "No, no, no. The point is, we are not giving them the generator technology and their not giving us the DHD", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You try this harebrained scheme and you blow yourself up for nothing. No way I'm hanging around for that", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-48-Hours.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Your plane leaves for that place in an hour", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-48-Hours.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Your new assignment is to supervise the development of that place's naqahdah generator program", "qsentId": 24}]